SAHASH SAINJU

WEB DEVELOPER

INFO

PHONE (925) 394 6737

EMAIL

sahash.sainju@roberthalf.com

LINKS

LinkedIn

Github Link

Personal website

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, javascript, AJAX, Rest API, JSON

Bootstrap 4, AngularJS, jQuery,

Google Analytics, Google Developer Tools

Word Press, Wix, Weebly, Joomla,

Ruby on Rails, Node, C++, Mean, Git

MongoDB, Active Record, MySQL, PostgreSQL

Agile Methodologies, TDD, BDD

Mocha, Chai, Rspec

Sublime Text, Github, Heroku, Bitbucket, Atom, Jira, Asana, Pivotal tracker

LANGUAGES

English

••••

Nepalese

••••

Hindi

• • • • •

PROFILE

Seeking new exciting opportunity to learn new technologies and come up with innovative problem solving techniques to build futuristic apps.

Full Stack Web Developer and CMS Product Manager with 8+years of experience in Web Development. Completed Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science with an addition of an Web Development Immersive Course from General Assembly in San Francisco, CA.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

CMS Product Manager, Robert Half International

San Ramon, CA

Nov 2016 - Present

Content management and governance on Intranet. Building sites, gathering business requirements and develop and manage content for clients to achieve their business goals. Collaboration with UX, Dev and Automation team to follow best practices to manage content on Intranet.

Technologies: Sharepoint Online, Outlook, Microsoft Office 365, javascript, CSS3, HTML5, jQuery, Photoshop, Sublime Text, Snagit,

Web Developer, Cibo Studios

San Francisco, CA

Mar 2016 - Nov 2019

UX/UI development, gathering requirements from client and managed software improvements. Agile work environment with tracking and finding detailed issues of the web pages and fixing it before delivering to client. Responsible for responsive designs and fulfilling the requirement of clients to meet their business goals.

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Mocha, Jira, javascript, CSS, jQuery, Asana, NodeJS

Web Developer / Web Design, Lumigrow

Novato, CA

Oct 2015 - Mar 2016

Followed agile methodology to break down tasks and testing software as well as hardware components for new product release. Pair Programming and wrote functional, unit and integrated testing.

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, javascript, Jira, jQuery, Mocha

Front End Developer, Humana Contractor

Louisville, KY

Mar 2013 - Apr 2015

Engaged in training with the teams clarifying business stories and ensuring business delivery and production turn. Participated in pair programming and TDD. Built iterated prototypes rapidly using customer feedback.

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, javascript, jQuery, Mocha, UI, MVC, Ruby on Rails

Web Developer / Web Design / UX Design, The White Zone Org

El Cerrito, CA

Apr 2015 - Apr 2016

Ensured the technical feasibility of the UI/UX designs. Managing events and collaborating with team members across the globe for data visualization. Designed banners, logos and flyers for social and cultural events.

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, javascript, jQuery, Photoshop, Sketch

Web Developer, Mountain State University (Intern)

Beckley, WV

Aug 2011 - Dec 2012

Designed and developed various college web pages and layouts. Pair Programming with senior team members developing the webpages.

Technologies: DreamWeaver, javascript, HTML, CSS, Photoshop

EDUCATION

Mountain State University, Associate's Degree in Computer Science

Beckley, WV

Jan 2009 - May 2011

Grantham University, Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Lenexa, KS

Jan 2012 - May 2015

General Assembly, Web Development Immersive Course

San Francisco, CA

May 2016 - Aug 2016

REFERENCES

Marilyn Murillo from Robert Half International

Marilyn.Murillo@roberthalf.com

Roja Sorokorensky from Robert Half International

roja.sorokorensky@roberthalf.com